<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ash&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/post.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ash&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 10:51:04 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Publish a Neovim Plugin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/post/how-to-publish-nvim-plugin.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 10:51:04 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/post/how-to-publish-nvim-plugin.html</guid>
      <description>Turning snippets into plugins that everyone can use Table of Contents The Structure of a Neovim Plugin Logic Dependencies and what they can do for you Publishing and Usage Conclusion Every Neovim power-user reaches a point when their init.lua becomes a mess of old code snippets. Since I use Markdown files every day for notes, planning and general writing, my breaking point was functions for Markdown formatting. I was tired of manually aligning Markdown tables and manually creating a Table of Contents for each file, along with streamlining embedding of hyperlinks and images.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stationary Wrap Up - 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/post/stationary.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:08:13 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/post/stationary.html</guid>
      <description>Physical Stationary That Brings Me Daily Enjoyment In a world where we use technology all day, I think using physical writing tools is really beneficial. I wake up every morning and write in my journal, about the day before. This helps me filter the important parts of the previous day in my mind, and also is a nice part of my daily routine that helps me stay active. In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll show the physical tools I use in my day to day life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>my-markdown</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/post/my-markdown.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 07:56:44 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/post/my-markdown.html</guid>
      <description>My relationship with markdown I use markdown every single day. It&amp;rsquo;s become an essential part of my workflow, and this started with note taking apps like Obsidian and Ulysses. When I found Neovim, everything changed. I started just making todo lists in markdown, within Neovim, and since all my notes were .md files, it was a really easy and natural way to organize my thoughts and things I had to do without switching context.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the beginning.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/post/my-first-post.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:56:44 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/post/my-first-post.html</guid>
      <description>This is my first post. I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to make a public blog on GH pages for such a long time, and I never got around to doing it. Now, I can finally say &amp;ldquo;ha check my blog&amp;rdquo;, and mean it.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m currently using Hugo as the brain for my blog, and a theme called hugo-brewm. It looks really nice, and I had Gemini replicate the demo layout because I found it really pretty.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
